Héctor Ramón Martínez de la Hoya

Spanish	
English C1	

Experienced professional with experience in all different areas of information technology. Developed communication, cooperation, and leadership skills. Knowledge of setting up a network or other system and experienced in performing maintenance on a regular basis.

SKILLS

- Extensive computer and network system experience, both in maintenance and initial setup.
- Excellent communication and service skills, able to build relationships and establish connections.
- Attention to small details and excellent critical thinking, decision making, management, and leadership skills.
- Computer Hardware Knowledge
- Computer Software Knowledge
- Operating Systems
- Troubleshooting

EDUCATION

2015 - 2020 B.S Biochemical Engineering.

Durango, México Instituto Tecnológico de Durango

2012 - 2015 **Programming Technician.**

Durango, México CBTis #130

WORK EXPERIENCE

2011 - Present

Self-Employment, Computer Repair Technician

Durango, México

- Carried out regular on-site repairs and preventive maintenance on PCs and the accompanying peripherals.
- Performed computer diagnostic, specifically to evaluate technical issues, at the same time, to solve customer concerns and to troubleshoot computer issues in a courteous and efficient manner.
- Customized personal computers to better serve customer needs.
- Scheduled work and ordered parts as well as completed repair invoices and estimates.

2015-2022

'Magdalena' Construction Company, Administrative Manager

Durango, México

- Supervised the activity of the workers.
- Conducted weekly meetings regarding ongoing projects.
- Performed administrative tasks as needed to supplement team activities.

COURSES

- ✓ Learn JavaScript ES9, HTML, CSS3 and NodeJS from scratch
- ✓ Modern JavaScript Ultimate Guide Build 15+ Projects
- ✓ Borderless Python: HTML, CSS, Flask, and MySQL
- ✓ React The Complete Guide: Hooks Context Redux MERN +15 Apps
- Digital Nomad Lifestyle: Live Your Dream & Travel the World
- ✓ Complete Digital Advertising Course: PPC Advertising Mastery
- ✓ Excel Professional 2022 For Companies!
- ✓ Excel University Basic, Intermediate and Advanced!